{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Locks placed by command are called ________ .", "opta": "implicit locks", "optb": "explicit locks", "optc": "exclusive locks", "optd": "shared locks", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following locks the item from change but not from read?", "opta": "Implicit lock", "optb": "Explicit lock", "optc": "Exclusive lock", "optd": "Shared lock", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following occurs when a transaction rereads data and finds new rows that were inserted by a command transaction since the prior read?", "opta": "Nonrepeatable read", "optb": "Phantom read", "optc": "Dirty read", "optd": "Consistent read", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A transaction for which all committed changes are permanent is called:", "opta": "atomic.", "optb": "consistent.", "optc": "isolated.", "optd": "durable.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In this instance, dirty reads are disallowed, while nonrepeatable reads and phantom reads are allowed.", "opta": "Read committed", "optb": "Read uncommitted", "optc": "Repeatable read", "optd": "Serializable", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following occurs when a transaction rereads data it has previously read and finds modification or deletions caused by a committed transaction?", "opta": "Nonrepeatable read", "optb": "Phantom read", "optc": "Dirty read", "optd": "Consistent read", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The advantage of optimistic locking is that:", "opta": "the lock is obtained only after the transaction has processed.", "optb": "the lock is obtained before the transaction has processed.", "optc": "the lock never needs to be obtained.", "optd": "transactions that are best suited are those with a lot of activity.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following refers to a cursor type that when the cursor is opened, a primary key value is saved for each row in the recordset; when the application accesses a row, the key is used to fetch the current values of the row?", "opta": "Forward only", "optb": "Static", "optc": "Keyset", "optd": "Dynamic", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following refers to a cursor type where changes of any type and from any source are visible?", "opta": "Forward only", "optb": "Static", "optc": "Keyset", "optd": "Dynamic", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following disallows both dirty reads and nonrepeatable reads, but allows phantom reads?", "opta": "Read committed", "optb": "Read uncommitted", "optc": "Repeatable read", "optd": "Serializable", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Dirty read, nonrepeatable, and phantom reads are not possible in this instance.", "opta": "Read committed", "optb": "Read uncommitted", "optc": "Repeatable read", "optd": "Serializable", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A transaction in which either all of the database actions occur or none of them do is called:", "opta": "atomic.", "optb": "consistent.", "optc": "isolated.", "optd": "durable.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A cursor type in which the application can only move forward through the recordset is called:", "opta": "forward only.", "optb": "static.", "optc": "keyset.", "optd": "dynamic.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following occurs when one transaction reads a changed record that has not been committed to the database?", "opta": "Nonrepeatable read", "optb": "Phantom read", "optc": "Dirty read", "optd": "Consistent read", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following allows dirty reads, nonrepeatable reads and phantom reads to occur?", "opta": "Read committed", "optb": "Read uncommitted", "optc": "Repeatable read", "optd": "Serializable", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following locks the item from access of any type?", "opta": "Implicit lock", "optb": "Explicit lock", "optc": "Exclusive lock", "optd": "Shared lock", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The size of a lock is called:", "opta": "implicit lock.", "optb": "lock granularity.", "optc": "exclusive lock.", "optd": "shared lock.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A cursor type in which the application sees the data as they were at the time the cursor was opened is called:", "opta": "forward only.", "optb": "static.", "optc": "keyset.", "optd": "dynamic.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the overall responsibility of the DBA?", "opta": "Facilitate the development and use of the database", "optb": "Create and populate tables", "optc": "Development, operation, and maintenance of the database and its applications", "optd": "Both the first and third answers above are correct.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Locks placed by the DBMS are called ________ .", "opta": "implicit locks", "optb": "explicit locks", "optc": "exclusive locks", "optd": "shared locks", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}